你干什么
Hey, what are you doing?
天哪
Jesus!
你看清肇事的车了吗
Did you get a good look?
只看到是辆蓝色丰田佳美
Blue Toyota Camry, it's all I saw.
是沃顿家的狗
It's the Wharton's dog.
-天哪  -他撑不了多久了
- Oh, man. - He's not gonna make it.
去看看他们在不在家
Go see if they're at home.
没事了
It's ok.
痛苦分两种
There are two kinds of pain.
一种让你变得更强...
The sort of pain that makes you strong...
另一种毫无价值
or useless pain...
只是徒添折磨
The sort of pain that's only suffering.
我对没价值的东西也没耐心
I have no patience for useless things.
这种时刻  需要有人采取行动
Moments like this require someone who will act...
或做一些不好的事
or do the unpleasant thing,
但也是必要的事
or the necessary thing.
好了...
There...
痛苦结束了
No more pain.
肇事逃逸  我很遗憾
It was a hit and run, I'm awfully sorry.
他肯定又自己跳出了庭院
He must have jumped over the fence again.
史蒂夫会就肇事车信息报案
Look, Steve's gonna file a report on the car,
他会派下属去处理
he'll put his people on it.
我们会找到那个司机的
We'll track him down.
你真是光彩照人
You're stunning.
我们走吧
Shall we?
三...二...一...
Three two...one...
新年快乐
Happy New Year!
当选总统  加勒特・沃克
Oh, President elected Garrett Walker.
我喜欢他吗  不
Do I like him? No.
我信任他吗  这不是重点
Do I believe in him? That's beside the point.
任何一个能获得七千万选票的政客
Any politician that gets 70 million votes
他所象征的含义早已超过了自身
has tapped into something larger than himself,
当然也超过了我  尽管我不愿意承认
larger than even me as much as I hate to admit it.
看那胜者的笑脸  那些信任的眼神
Look at that winning smile, those trusting eyes.
我一早便抓住了他  并扮演了重要角色
I clung to him early on, and made myself vital.
在国会待了22年
After 22 years in congress
我能嗅到风头的走向
I can smell which way the wind is going.
吉姆・马修斯  尊敬的副总统阁下
Jim Matthews, his right honorably Vice-President.
前宾夕法尼亚州州长
Former Governor of Pennsylvania.
他帮总统拿下了宾州
He did his duty in delivering the Keystone State.
上帝保佑他
Bless his heart.
现在他们想让他退休了
And now they're about to put him out to pasture.
但他看上去挺开心的  不是吗
But he looks happy, now doesn't he?
在有些人看来  就是椅子大点罢了
For some, it's simply the size of the chair.
琳达・瓦斯奎兹  沃克的幕僚长
Linda Vasquez, Walker's chief of staff.
是我找来了她  她是个女人
I got her hired. She's a woman, check.
又是拉丁裔
And a Latina, check.
但更重要的是  她像一块廉价牛排一样坚韧
But more important than that, she's as tough as two-dollar steak.
样样都符合标准
Check, check, check.
要入住白宫
When it comes to the White House,
你不仅要揣好钥匙
you not only need the keys in your back pocket.
还需要一个看门人
You need the gatekeeper.
而我  我只是卑微的众议院多数党党鞭
As for me, I'm just a lowly house majority whip.
我维持这个被琐事
I keep things moving in a Congress
和倦怠堵塞的众议院的运转
choked by pettiness, and lassitude.
我的工作就是疏通管道  让污泥流动
My job is to clear the pipes, and keep the sludge moving.
但我这水管工要退休了  我尽了职责
But I won't have to be a plumber much longer. I've done my time.
我支持了对的人
I backed the right man.
付出与索取
Give and take.
这就是华盛顿
Welcome to Washington.
你该理发了
You need a haircut.
是吗
You think?
稍修剪一下
A little trim.
你准备穿什么
What are you gonna wear?
-去会面吗  -正式宣布的时候
- You mean for the meeting? - For the announcement.
我准备穿海军蓝  带细条纹的那套
I'm wearing my navy blue, the one with the pinstripes.
很好
Good.
那套西服很衬你
You look handsome in that suit.
难说他们会不会在你的董事会前宣布
I don't know if they will announce it before your board meeting.
只要这笔捐款保证能拿到就行
Well, as long as I can say the donation is coming.
一正式宣布  桑科公司就会给你支票
As soon as it's official, Sancorp will write you the check.
今年对我们将会是重要的一年
This is going to be a big year for us.
哪一个委员会
Community of what?
我猜是移民  银行或者教育  但是...
I would say immigration, banking or education, but...
但我常规的联络人都无法确认
None of my regular sources can confirm that.
那...
Because...
他们是不知道  还是不愿说
They don't know, or because they're not talking?
他们不知道
Because they don't know.
继续查  挖点东西出来
Keep at it, get me something.
对不起  真抱歉  汉默施密特先生
Sorry, I'm so sorry Mr. Hammerschmidt.
我是佐伊...
Zoe...
-巴恩斯  -嗯
- Barnes - Right.
他当年也过了一年才记住你是谁吗
Did it take him a year to remember your name?
不止
Longer.
早上好  卢卡斯
Good morning, Lucas.
有什么事吗  佐伊
What can I do for you, Zoe?
我受不了费尔法克斯的郡议会了
I am sick of the Fairfax county council.
-你每天都这么说  -让我做网络报道
- You tell me everyday. - Move me online.
让我开博客
My own blog.
第一人称  主观视角  五百字篇幅
First person, subjective, 500 words.
-没门  -我去挖掘秘密
- Not gonna happen. - I'll go underground.
幕后消息  甚至去翻夜壶
backrooms, the urinals!
去争取国会的人
I'll win over staff members on the Hill.
他们也需要发泄
They need a place to vent.
-八卦专栏  -不  是事实真相
- A gossip column? - No. We'll lift the veil.
现在到底怎么回事
What's really going on.
这里是《华盛顿先驱报》  佐伊
This is the Washington Herald, Zoe.
不是...名人消息网
It's not...TMZ.
你知道有多少人浏览名人消息网吗
Do you know how many people who watch TMZ?
我一点也不关心
I couldn't care less.
所以报刊新闻业在衰落
Which is why print journalism is dying.
那也不失体面  至少这份报纸是如此
Then it will die with dignity. At least with this paper.
你还活在20世纪吧  卢卡斯
You are stuck in the 20th century, Lucas,
缺乏想象力
you lack imagination.
也许吧  但我现在不需要想象力
Maybe so, but right now I don't need imagination,
我需要报道
I need copy.
你自己的时间随意支配
Your nights and weekends are yours,
你想做什么我都没意见
I applaud whatever you want to do,
但不能占用工作时间
as long as its not on my time.
-你是让我去干活儿吗  -没错
- You're telling me to go back to work? - I am.
但你实际上是叫我滚蛋
What you're really telling me is to fuck off.
两者都有
I'm telling you both.
普罗旺斯基金的查普曼先生在等你
It's Mr. Chapman already, from Provence Trust.
不要接进电话  克里斯蒂娜
Hold my calls, Christina.
亨利
Henry.
见到你真好
It's good to see you.
-到这儿几天了  -今天刚来
- How long are you in town for? - Just today.
那你一定得来看就职典礼
What? You gotta come back down for the inauguration.
我可以帮你联系一下
I can hook you up.
不如帮我联系一下
How about you hook me up with
你答应会修改的分区法吧
the zoning laws you promised to get changed?
为了一块不能建房的空地
We got 12 millions sitting in escrow
我们一千二百万被托管
for an empty lot we can't build on.
我知道  但你要明白
I know, but you gotta understand...
这是地方政府的问题
It's a local municipal issue.
我不能随便打个电话就...
I can't just pick up the phone...
你不能了吗
You can't?
你求我们捐款五万的时候
Because that's not what you lead us to believe
可不是这么说的
when you begged for 50 grand in donations.
嗯  我
Right, I...
稍等片刻
Just one second.
克里斯蒂娜  我说了不要转接
Christina, I said no calls,
我和查普曼先生会面时不接电话
not while I'm meeting with Mr. Chapman.
当选总统
The President-elect?
-你不介意吧  -不  接吧
- Do you mind? - No, go ahead please.
把电话接进来  克里斯蒂娜
Put him trough Christina.
当选总统先生
Mr. President-elect?
谢谢
Thank you.
是的  我们很高兴以两位数优势胜出
Yes, we were pleased to win by double digits.
当然  乐意效劳
Absolutely, anything you need.
我需要你把你湿长灵活的舌头
I need you to put your long, wet, talented tongue
伸入我两腿之间
between my tights
让我像莫妮卡・莱温斯基那样尖...
and make me squeal like Monica Lewin...
我也是
Me too.
好的  谢谢您  先生
Okay, thank you, sir.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry...
刚才说到哪了
where were we?
沃克
Walker...
他什么样
what's he like?
当选总统迟到了吗
The President-elect running late?
不  他来不了  我会跟他汇报的
No, he couldn't make it. I'll brief him, though.
好的
Okay.
这是我起草的备忘录
This is the memo, I've drafted,
关于我们在商讨的中东政策
on our Middle East policy we've been developing.
我想借用里根的说法
Now, I want to borrow from Reagan.
造个新词  叫"滴入式外交"
I'd like to coin the phrase "Trickle-down diplomacy".
-这样  -弗兰克  我得打断你
- That way... - Frank. I'm gonna stop you there.
我们不打算提名你为国务卿
We are not nominating you for the Secretary of State.
我知道他向你承诺过
I know, he made you a promise,
但现在情况有变
but circumstances have changed.
所谓承诺  琳达
The nature of promises, Linda,
就是不论情况如何变化也不受影响
is that they remain immune to changing cicumstances.
加勒特已经深思熟虑过了
Garrett has thought long and hard about this.
他认为我们需要你留在国会
And he's decided we need you to stay in Congress.
这是什么时候的决定
When was this decision made?
为什么我没参与商讨
And why wasn't I part of a conversation?
我很抱歉  弗兰克  如果由我决定
I'm sorry, Frank, if it been up to me,
我也不会等到现在才告诉你
I wouldn't have waited this long to tell you.
那你早就知道要这么做
So you knew, you were going to do this.
我们的确谈了很久
It has been an evolving discussion.
这就是懦夫的做法
It's a chicken-shit move.
-弗兰克  -我都做过审查了
- Frank... - I was vetted.
-那都是晃我吗  -不是的
- Was that a ruse? - No.
我们打开天窗说亮话
Let's be absolutely clear,
没有我  你们赢不了
you wouldn't have won without me.
你说的没错  但我们现在执政了
You're right, but now we have to lead.
所以得做出艰难的决定
And that means making tough choices.
你知道  教育是我们的重中之重
As you know, education is a top priority for us.
要进行彻底的改革
A complete federal overhaul.
但不仅仅是教育  弗兰克
But it's not just the education, Frank,
国会已经分裂了
Congress has split.
我们更需要你待在国会  而不是国务院
We need you there, more than we need you in the State Department.
是我找你来的  琳达
I got you hired, Linda.
我知道
I know.
捐款  博取公开支持
Donations, endorsements.
我为竞选写了整套外交纲领
I wrote the campaign's entire foreign policy platform.
我把外事委员会多年来...
I bring years of Foreign Affairs Committee...
弗兰克
Frank.
请别这样
Please.
我要单独和沃克谈
I want to speak to Walker personally.
已经决定了
The decision is made.
我们需要你  弗兰克
We need you, Frank.
你会支持我们吗
Will you stand beside us or not?
当然了  如果这是总统所愿
Of course, if that's what the President wants.
很高兴听到这话
I'm very glad to hear that.
我很好奇
I'm curious.
你们选了谁
If not me then who?
迈克尔・科恩
Michael Kern.
Michael Kern?
嗯
Well...
真是绝妙的选择
that is an excellent choice.
净水计划
这样清楚吗
Do you think it'll look clear?
我可不想让这看着像
I just want to make sure it doesn't look like
我们在忽略国内...
we're neglecting out domestic...
不不不  我会说
No, no, no, no... I'm gonna say
-我们在拓展业务  -好的
- that we are expanding our mission. - Okay.
我们会启用新的组织帮助我们
And we're bringing on a new organization to help us.
决定好用哪家了吗
They know which one yet?
我还在定夺  但是
I'm still looking into a few options, but, um...
我们之前说定要招几个新人
Tell me, what did we agree on that we could hire how many new people.
-六个吗  -六七个吧
- Six? - Six, maybe seven.
人手足够的
We'll have enough.
真激动人心啊
Ooh, it's exciting. Huh?
向着新方向前进
This, uh, new direction we're heading.
我只是不知道要怎么安置那些人
I just don't know where we're gonna fit all the people.
你觉得我们地方不够用吗
Well, do you think we'll have to look into additional space?
不不  我会想办法
No, no. I'll find a way.
好  去修改PPT
Okay, so make the changes to the power point.
-两点半开会  -好的
- And let's meet again, at 2:30. - Okay.
是我
It's me.
我像傻子一样给你留言  打给我
I feel like an idiot leaving messages like this. Call me back.
什么事  佐伊
What is it, Zoe?
我知道你在白宫会很忙  所以
Um, I knew you're gonna have your hands full at the White House. So,...
如果你需要谁来做调查  或者
If you need someone to do research, or...
-写背景资料  -我没问题
- Or punch out background. - I think I'll be fine.
如果实在忙不过来  需要帮助的话...
Well, if things get hectic, and you need any help...
你好写博客说跟大人物打过交道了吗
So you can blog about rubbing shoulders with the big boys.
卢卡斯跟你说了什么
Wh... What did Lucas tell you?
无意冒犯  佐伊
Look, no offence, Zoey,
但我没时间教菜鸟
But I don't have time to be anyone's training wheels.
我只是想
I just thought...
我只想帮帮你
No, I was just actually offering to lend a hand.
-仅此而已  -知道了
- That's it. - I got it.
谢谢
Thanks.
克莱尔  你在哪
-卡莱尔  -你没打电话
- Claire. - You didn't call.
-我...  -你没打电话  弗兰西斯
- I was... - You didn't call me, Francis.
九小时  没一个电话
Nine hours, you don't not call me.
这可是天大的事
Not when it's this big.
是的
You're right.
我们什么时候逃避过对方了
When have we ever avoided each other?
我想先想个办法出来
I wanted a solution first.
-想到了吗  -还没有
- Do you have one? - Not yet.
这对我也有影响  弗兰西斯
This affects me too, Francis.
我不是为钱的事生气
And it's not the money I'm upset about.
而是我们该共同面对
It's that we do things together.
你不告诉我  我们就完了
When you don't involve me we are in free fall.
我该打给你的  可我没有
I should have called you and I didn't.
发生了什么
What Happened?
她说他们得把我留在议会
She says they needed to keep me in Congress.
-琳达说的吗  -沃克都没在场
- Linda said that? - Walker wasn't even there.
这是最让我生气的
That's what really get's me,
他都没胆直视我的眼睛
he didn't even have the courage to look me in the eye.
你不该信任那女人的
I knew you shouldn't trust that women.
我不信任她  我不信任任何人
I didn't. I don't. I don't trust any one.
那你怎么没预料到呢
Then how could you not see this coming.
我没想到他们敢这么做
I never thought they were capable.
你很少低估别人啊  弗兰西斯
You don't usually underestimate people, Francis.
我知道
I know.
狂妄
Hubris...
-野心  -你该觉得愤怒
- Ambition ... - You should be angry.
-我都气疯了  -那我怎么不觉得
- I am livid. - Then where is that I don't see it.
你想让我怎样  大吼大叫吗
What do you want me to do, scream and yell?
-大发脾气吗  -我想看你有所表现
- Throw a temper? - I want more than I'm seeing.
你不止这点出息  弗兰西斯
You're better than this, Francis.
我很抱歉  克莱尔  很抱歉
Well, I'm sorry, Claire. I am sorry.
不  我不接受
No, that I won't accept.
-什么  -道歉
- What? - Apologies.
我丈夫从不道歉
My husband doesn't apologizes.
即便对我
Even to me.
你起来多久了
How long have you been up?
好几个小时
Hours.
我知道该怎么做
I know what I have to do.
很好
Good.
我们将度过很多这样的夜晚
We'll have a lot of nights like this.
制定计划
Making plans.
没时间睡觉
Very little sleep.
这我知道
I expected that.
我不担心这个
It doesn't worry me.
我得去忙了
I'd better get to work.
我在楼上给你准备了一套西服
I laid a suit out for you upstairs.
海军蓝那套
The navy blue one.
我爱那个女人
I love that woman.
甚于鲨鱼爱鲜血
I love her more than sharks love blood.
当选总统加勒特・沃克
The President-elect Garrett Walker...
沃克提名科罗拉多资浅参议员科恩入主国务院
你说他们为什么选他
Why do you think they went with him?
我们太好了  他们需要我们在国会的支持
We are too good, they can't afford to lose us in Congress.
他整过容
He's had work done.
可能收过下巴  头发绝对是染的
Chin tuck probably. Definitely dyes his hair.
-我们要说什么吗  -千万别
- Do we say anything? - No. God no.
-除非他提起来  -南茜
- Not unless he brings it up. - Nancy?
-9点20分  -全都取消  斯坦普你进来
- 9:20... - Cancel everything. Stanford, you're with me.
听着
Now, look...
他们帮了我们一个大忙  道格
They've done us a great favor, Doug.
我们不必再忠于他们  不效忠任何人
We are no longer bond by allegiances. We serve no one.
今后我们只有一条准则
We live by one rule, and one rule only
绝不再陷入如此境地
never again will we allow ourselves to be put in such a position.
沃克和瓦斯奎兹
Walker and Vasquez?
所有人  他们都跑不了
All of them. I hold them all accountable.
-报复吗  -不  不对
- Retribution? - No, no!
不止
It's more than that.
退后一步
Take a step back.
统观全局
Look at the bigger picture.
我明白你什么意思了
I can see what you're getting at.
先拿科恩开刀
Kern first?
吞噬鲸鱼就要这样  道格
That's how you devour a whale, Doug.
一口一口来
One bite at a time.
你想要谁
Who would you want?
-做国务卿  -给我列个候选人表
- For Secretary of State. - Give me a list of choices.
不管我们打算怎么做  得找个中间人
And, however we do this, we'll also need a buffer.
找个傀儡吗
You mean an errand boy?
是的  一个完全受我们控制的人
Yes, someone we control completely.
-好  我会留意的  -好
- Okay. I'll keep my ear to the ground. - Good.
我一天没吃东西了
I haven't eaten since yesterday.
我都快不忍心了
I almost pity him.
他也不想做我的盘中肉
He didn't choose to be put on my platter.
等到我把他剁碎了喂狗
When I carve him up and toss him to the dogs,
他才会承认那残忍的不可避免的真相
only then will he confront that brutal inescapable truth.
上帝啊
My God!
原来我不过是一盘猪肠
All I ever amounted to is chitterlings..
自卑的必升为高
"And he that shall humble himself, shall be exalted."
马太福音  第23章  第12节
Matthew, Chapter 23 verse 12.
感谢上帝
Thanks be to God.
今天我想讲的是
I'd like to speak today on the subject of
谦逊
humility.
你们大部分人刚刚赢得了改选
Well, a lot of you have just won re-election.
否则  大概也不会坐在这儿了
If you hadn't, you might not be sitting here.
我们当然应该享受成功并心怀感激
And of course we should enjoy our success and be grateful for it.
但千万不要让感激变为
But never let your gratitude sour into
骄傲
pride.
接下来的几年  你们会面对很多挑战
You will have many challenges ahead over the next couple of years.
一个人的品行
And a person's character
不取决于这人如何享受胜利
isn't determined by how he or she enjoys vitory
而在于这人如何忍受失败
but rather how he or she endures defeat.
没什么比信仰更能支撑我们度过艰难时光了
Nothing can help us endure dark times better than our faith.
克莱尔
Claire.
-你好  费莉希蒂  -你好吗
- Hello, Felicity. - How are you?
-很好  你呢  -很好
- Good, how are you ? - Good.
我很遗憾  这根本就没道理
I'm sorry, it's just not right.
我和查尔斯根本无法理解沃克是怎么想的
Charles and I can't understand what Walker was thinking.
你真是太贴心了
Oh, that's very sweet.
可是实事上  只跟你说
But, really, between you and me,
我觉得弗兰西斯如释重负
I think Francis is relieved.
他在国会更如鱼得水
He just feels much more at home in Congress.
在这之前  我敢压一百万赌他们选你
I would've bet a million dollars they were gonna pick you.
幸好你不差这一百万
Well, it's good thing you have a million dollars to spare.
但你显然是唯一人选啊
But you are by far and away the only choice.
谢谢你这么说
I appreciate you saying that.
迈克尔只有一半的经验...
I mean, Michael? Come on, he's got half the experience...
加勒特是个聪明人  他心里有数
Garrett is a smart man, he knows what he's doing.
弗兰克  你可比我强
You're a better man than I, Frank.
你
You...
想要点红酒吗
You want some of that wine?
好啊  当然
Yes, definitely.
这酒还真不错  你哪弄来的
Man this is some good shit, where did you get it?
我其实是
I kinda lifted it...
从议长节日派对的贵宾室偷的
from the VIP room of the speaker's holiday party.
真了不起
I'm impressed.
波尔多20年陈酿
Bordeaux twenty years old?
这酒和你很般配
It seemed about right for you.
-这话什么意思  -我快30了
- Why would you say that to me? - I'm almost thirty.
就你而言算很老了
Pratically ancient in your book.
我不介意年龄啊
I don't discriminate when it comes to age.
是吗  你什么时候雇过40岁的员工
Really? When was the last time you hired a 40 years old staffer?
-不代表我不会雇  -只要她床技了得
- Doesn't mean I wouldn't. - As long as she's good in the sack.
-拜托  -我说错了吗
- Come on. - That's true, isn't it?
你这是唱的哪一出
Where is this coming from?
你不会为哪个刚从瓦萨学院毕业的小骚货
You are not gonna just toss me aside for some sluts
把我扔一边吧
straight out of Vassar?
原来是为这个
So we're having that conversation.
已经六个月了  不再是玩玩而已了
It's been six month. It's not a little office fling any more.
你想让我说那三个有魔力的字
You want me to say those three magic words.
其中一个还以L开头
One of which starts with an L.
-不是  -好吧
- No. - Okay.
我要说了
I'll say it.
克里斯蒂娜・盖拉格
Christina Gallagher,
舔我蛋
lick my balls.
你个混蛋
You're a bastard!
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你  克里斯蒂娜
I love you, Christina.
我也爱你
I love you.
现在能舔我的蛋了吗
Now will you lick my balls?
我想知道
So I'm curious,
我们算资助人  捐助者还是讨厌鬼
are we patrons, benefactors or lepers?
不管你信不信  我们是天使
Believe it not, we're angels.
我要出去假装打电话
I'm gonna go outside and pretend to use my cell phone.
去吧
Go.
国家表演艺术中心
我能借你的外套吗
Could I have your jacket?
你要来睡觉吗
Are you coming to bed?
我一会儿就上去
I'll be up in a bit.
-别熬通宵了  -不会  我马上就去
- Don't stay up all night. - No, I'll be right there.
非常感谢  回头给你打电话
Thanks so much. I'll call you.
等等  你玩得不开心吗
Wait... I thought you had a good time?
开心  我很喜欢  我从没去过那儿
Oh I did, I loved it. I've never been before.
或许我能上去坐坐
Well, maybe I could come up.
布莱恩  你人真好
Brian, you're so sweet, really.
但如果我要上你  你会知道的
But if I was gonna fuck you, you'd know.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
想要别人瞧得起你  就别只穿条丁字裤
国会议员弗兰西斯・安德伍德  众议院多数党党鞭
我看他挺严肃的
-她来了  -让她进来
- She's here. - Send her in.
总统的幕僚长可极少亲临国会
It's quite rare for a president's chief of staff to climb the Hill.
无疑是表示尊重
A gesture of respect no doubt,
或者是出于绝望
or desperation.
我猜她会提名唐纳德・布莱斯负责教育改革
I'm guessing she'll say Donald Blythe for education.
看看我说的对不对
Let's see if I'm right.
早上好  琳达
Good morning, Linda.
非常感谢你走这一趟
Thank you so much for making the trip up.
不客气
Of course, my pleasure.
教育
Education.
先说重要的
First things first,
这是就职典礼的座位图
the seating chart for the inauguration.
你和克莱尔坐这儿怎么样
How do these two work for you and Claire?
还附赠杰弗逊舞会的入场券
They come with a complimentary set of tickets to the Jefferson Ball.
克莱尔会非常高兴的
Claire would be over the moon.
那真是太好了
Good, I'm so glad.
那么  教育改革
So... education.
我们让唐纳德・布莱斯拟草案
We have Donald Blythe drafting the legislation.
唐纳德・布莱斯  天啊
Donald Blythe? Jesus.
我知道
I know.
你想要个比马克思还左的法案吗
So you want a bill just two steps left of Karl Marx.
我向当选总统提过反对意见
I advised the President-elect against it,
但唐纳德是教育界代表人物
but Donald is the face of education.
他为促成改革奋斗25年了
He's been pushing reforms for 25 years.
你想让我把他往中间引
You want me to guide him to the middle?
我们需要一部能通过的法案
We need a bill we can pass.
我在这事上有绝对自主权和决定权吗
Do I have absolute autonomy and authority on this?
不止如此
There's more.
加勒特想在就职百天内对法案进行投票
Garrett wants the bill on the floor in the first 100 days.
他想在就职演说中做出承诺
He wants to make a pledge in his inaugural address.
那...
Ah, that's...
真是非常有雄心  琳达
That's very ambitious, Linda.
我们能做出承诺吗
Can we make that pledge?
一百天吗
A hundred days?
我可以实现
I can deliver.
保持联系
Keep me posted.
我会找唐纳德谈  这周晚些时候和你联系
I'll talk with Donald, I'll check in with you later in the week.
好极了
Terrific.
你闻到了吗
Did you smell that?
装模作样  假意顺从
The smugness? The false deference.
她以为两张票就能收买我
She thinks I can be bought with a pair of tickets.
我是个战后柏林的妓女吗
What am I a whore in post-war Berlin
眼馋那点免费长袜和巧克力
salivating over free stocking and chocolate?
她想要的东西  代价要高得多
What she's asking will cost far more than that.
-费格森  -太老了
- Ferguson. - Too old.
-威利斯  -太蠢了
- Willis? - Too stupid.
-博伊德  -太基了
- Boyd. - Too queer.
不是吧
Really?
他都结婚  育有三子了
He's married with three kids.
他们肯定要伤心死了
And wouldn't they be devastated.
好吧
All right.
凯瑟琳・杜兰特呢
What about Catherine Durant?
凯茜・杜兰特
Cathy Durant ...
她曾公开反沃克
She was vocally anti Walker.
她有经验
She's got the experience.
替我安排会面
Set up a meeting.
桑科公司的捐款
The donation from Sancorp...
那笔钱得另想办法了
The money will have to come from somewhere else.
天哪  怎么回事
God, what happened?
我看了13年的预算
I've looked over the budget for fiscal 13
其中160万是员工工资
and we've allocated 1.6 million for salaries.
我们要把这项支出减半
We need to cut that in half.
-什么  你是说  -伊芙琳
- What, you're suggesting... - Evelyn,
我们要裁员
we're going to let some people go.
裁掉一半吗
That would be half of our staff?
我们必须腾出些位置
We have to carve out some room.
但这样就得裁掉些从一开始
But you'll have to fire some essential people
就跟着我们的老员工啊
who have been with us since the beginning.
我们是慈善机构
We are a charity,
但不服务于职员
but not for our employees.
克莱尔  要知道一直以来
You know, um, Claire, I have held my tongue
我没对国际化的事发表意见
about this whole international thing for a while.
但我想不通
But, I don't get it.
为什么要放弃现有熟悉的业务
I mean, we're really good at what we do,
转而做一些我们不在行的事情呢
why do we have to try and be something we're not?
因为发展到了瓶颈  伊芙琳
Because we've plateaued, Evelyn,
这个机构  现在应当...
and it is time for us, for our entire organisation...
去非洲挖井吗  我们对此一无所知
But digging wells in Africa? We don't know anything about that.
因此我们需要雇佣新员工
Which is why we have to bring in new people.
这是我向董事会提出的规划
This is the plan that I've proposed to the Board
董事会也接受了
and we are moving forward with it.
记得给我名单
I'd like a list of names, please.
克莱尔  不能再斟酌一下吗
Claire, can we just think about this?
我已经想过了
I have thought about it.
这是斟酌再三的结果
I've put a lot of thought into it.
-但是我觉得我们真的  -伊芙琳
- Yeah, but I think that we can really... - Evelyn ...
你是办公室主任
You are the office manager.
你得相信  我心里有数
I need you to trust that I know what I'm doing.
所以  请尽快给我那份名单
So please, get me that list, as soon as possible.
-女士  您不能  -抱歉
- Oh, ma'am. You can't go... - I'm sorry, I just ...
-我只有一个问题  -不行
- I just have one question... - No.
先生  抱歉  这位女士
Sir, I apologize this woman...
-议员  -小姐  请您退后
- Congressman. - Miss you need to step away from him.
-我只打扰一会  -请退后
- If I could just have one second. - You step away from the...
你是谁
Who are you?
我是佐伊・巴恩斯  《华盛顿先驱报》记者
My name is Zoe Barnes, I'm a reporter at the Washington Herald.
现在已经过了晚上十点半  而且这是我家
It is after 10:30 at night and this is my home.
我不允许任何...
I do not allow any...
你我彼此欣赏
We are part of a mutual admiration society.
你喜欢交响乐
You're a fan of the symphony.
比起音乐  更喜欢观众
One more for the people watching than the music.
没事了  史蒂夫  巴恩斯小姐  请进
It's all right, Steve. Come on in, Miss Barnes.
这酒很烈
It's strong.
你想要淡一些的
You prefer weak?
不  越烈越好
No, the stronger the better.
看看没什么
There's no harm in looking.
低级的把戏
It's a cheap ploy.
低级却有效
It's cheap but effective.
我洗耳恭听
Well, you certainly have my undivided attention.
好  我来这里的原因
Good. The reason I'm here...
前戏这就结束了
Oh, is foreplay over?
我听说肯尼迪撑不过3分钟
I read somewhere that JFK never lasted more than three minutes.
所以呢
The point been?
时间很宝贵
Time is precious.
身居高位之人无暇前戏
Powerful people don't have the luxury of foreplay.
那说说你的目的吧  巴恩斯小姐
Okay, so why are you here, Ms. Barnes?
我要找能说话的人
I need somebody I can talk to.
我们就在说话  你想说点什么
We're talking. Tell me what we're talking about.
我会为你保密  你说什么我都发表
I protect your identity. I print whatever you tell me.
而且绝不乱问问题
And I'll never ask any questions.
那你凭什么认定
And what makes you think
我没有和你的同行
I don't already have such an arrangement
达成了类似协议呢
with one of your colleague.
那样你就不会让我进门
Because if you did, you wouldn't have let me through the door.
在我漫长  成功的事业里
I've led a very long, very successful career
我一直避免与媒体打这种交道
avoiding this sort of intrigue with the press.
我现在也没觉得有什么好处
I can't see any advantage in starting now...
-那有什么坏处呢  -至少不谨慎
- But is there any disadvantage? - Sloppiness, for one.
我会绝对谨慎小心的
I promise you absolute discretion.
那就涉及到信任了
So, we're talking about trust.
随便你怎么说
Use whatever words you like.
怎么说很重要  巴恩斯小姐
Words matter very much, Ms. Barnes.
做你这行  对措词更当注意
You should care more about them, given your profession.
那么  是的
Then, yes...
我想获得你的信任
Your trust.
那我要信任哪个佐伊・巴恩斯呢
So, which Zoey Barnes am I to trust?
报道消防员娶开停车罚单女警的记者
The one who wrote about the fireman that married the meter maid?
还是那篇格外精彩的
Or the one who authored a very fine article
石溪公园新慢跑路线的作者
on a new jogging path in Rockcreek Park?
别太得意  我什么都读
Don't be flattered, I read everything.
我能写的远超过他们让我写的
I'm better than what they have me doing.
你也深有体会
You know what that feels like.
是吗
Do I?
如果你当选国务卿  一定能做得很好
You would've made a great Secretary of State.
你到底想问什么  巴恩斯小姐
How exactly may I help you, Miss Barnes?
你一定知道新政府的立法议程
You must know the administration legislative agenda.
-第一项是什么  -我可能知道
- What's coming up first? - I may.
-可以告诉我吗  -你觉得是什么
- Will you tell me? - What would be your guess?
-教育  -为什么
- Education. - Why?
移民问题争议太大
Immigration is too controversial,
税收改革不够劲爆
a tax reform isn't sexy enough.
关于孩子的能得到所有人支持
Everyone can get behind children.
-是教育吗  -怎么想是你的自由
- Is it education? - You might very well think that
我不能发表意见
I couldn't possibly comment.
给个提示吧
A hint.
很晚了  巴恩斯小姐
It's late, Miss Barnes.
我们还能再见吗
Can we talk again?
请你谅解  但这些事我得想想
I hope you'll understand that I want to sleep on all of this.
我从不在深更半夜
I never make such big decision so long after sunset
做重大决定
and so far from dawn.
我手机号在背面
My cell phone's on the back.
巴恩斯小姐的名字记入来访登记簿了吗
Did you put Miss Barnes in the visitor's ledger?
-还没  -那就别记
- Not yet. - Don't.
-不用说  -是的
- Needless to say. - Needless.
你们好
Hello.
克莱尔
Claire.
这是《华盛顿先驱报》的佐伊・巴恩斯小姐
This is Miss Zoe Barnes of the Washington Herald.
她正准备离开
She was just leaving.
幸会  安德伍德太太
Very nice to meet you, Mrs. Underwood.
开车小心  路面结冰了
Drive safe, there's a lot of ice on the road.
好的
I will.
谢谢
Thank you.
这招真的管用吗
Does that work on anybody?
什么
Does what?
魔术胸罩和V领衬衫
The push-up bra and V-neck T.
据我所知不管用
Well, if it does, I don't know who they are.
没事的  没事
Ok, it's all right, it's all right.
驾照和行驶证
License and registration.
在仪表板的储物箱里  亲爱的
The glove compartment, sweetheart.
这不是驾照  是星巴克的卡
This isn't your driver's license, it's a Starbucks' card.
见鬼  抱歉
Oh, shit. Sorry.
你喝了什么吗  先生
Sir, have you been drinking?
没有  我这个点从不喝咖啡
No, I never drink coffee at this hour.
请你下车
I'm gonna need you to step out of the car.
如果是超速  开个罚单就得了
Hey, I was speeding you can write me a ticket...
请下车  先生
Sir, step out of the car.
现在就下车
Right now.
我也不想这样  但我是国会议员
Look, I don't wanna be a prick, but I'm a member of the Congress.
你是中国国王也没用
I don't care if you are the king of China.
中国没有国王
China doesn't have a king.
那是共产主义寡头政治
It's a communist oligarchic.
-瓜...寡...寡...  -快下车
- Oil... oliguarch ... - Let's go, out.
-你也是  亲爱的  -妈的  真难念
- You too, sweetie. - Fuck, that's hard to say.
喂
Hello?
很好
Good.
把他弄出来吧
Well, let's get him out.
我能坐这儿吗
Mind if I join you?
在搞什么鬼
What the fuck is going on?
-我不是要和...  -不是
- I thought I was meeting with... - No.
是和我见面
You're meeting me.
该死的  现在是凌晨四点
It's four in the goddamned morning.
我还要去市议会开会
I've got a City Council meeting...
你当警察局长多久了
You've been Police Commissioner for what?
快十年了吧
Almost a decade now?
我们是来谈我的简历吗
We're here to talk about my resume?
把"华盛顿市长"放在简历里不错吧
"Mayor of DC" would look good on that resume, wouldn't it?
我们知道你早有此意
We know that you've been angling to run for some time.
经验丰富是你的优势
Experience is your strong suit.
但博取公开支持和筹资
Indorsement, fund raising...
你不行
they're not.
我们可以帮你
We can help with that.
罗素
Russo.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
喝了点酒而已
It was just a few drinks.
-都被警察拦下了  -又不是醉得很厉害
- It was enough to get pulled over. - I wasn't drunk drunk.
你当时一个人吗
Were you alone?
是的
Yes.
-看着我说  -注意看路
- Say it to my face. - Watch the road.
看着我说
Say it to my face!
是的
Yes.
我一个人
I was alone.
你不能再这样了  彼得
You can not keep doing this, Peter.
会让你吃不了兜着走
It's going to catch up with you.
我知道
I know.
杰弗逊舞会上
Do you think we can arrange two more
我们那桌能再加两个人吗
at our table for the Jefferson Ball?
-加谁  -霍博恩夫妇
- For who? - The Holburnes.
你为什么要找他们去
Why on earth would you want them there?
净水计划需要她的捐款
I'm gonna need her money for the CWI,
光裁员还不够
the staff cuts were just not enough.
我跟瓦斯奎兹说说
I'll talk to Vasquez.
-情况如何  -不错  有进展
- How are we doing? - Good. Progress.
铁烧得正热
Irons on the fire.
我喜欢铁
I like irons,
但更爱火
but I love fire.
好的
Yes.
你这是...
What are you...
你的草案是一纸垃圾  唐纳德
The bill is garbage, Donald.
增加税收  限制半私立学校
Tax increases, ban on vouchers,
增强联邦政府监管
federal oversight.
你怎么能指望我让它通过...
How do you expect me to get that through a...
但是琳达让我来写  她还允诺
But Linda told me to write it, she promise...
她肯定做了不少保证
I'm sure she said any number of things,
把那些都忘了吧  唐纳德
forget what they promised you, Donald.
他们要的是你的名字  因为它份量够重
They want your name because it carrys weight.
我的想法奠定我的名声
Well my name comes with my ideas.
我能理解  但你也得讲理
I understand, but you got to be reasonable.
这不是废奴问题的辩论
This isn't the Great Debate.
我们得让好的改革法案通过
It's about passing meaningful reform,
也许与你的期望有出入  但是
maybe not everything you would've hope, but...
与我方便  与你方便
help me, help you.
我需要时间琢磨
That's gonna take time.
那些想法  我都考虑...
Those ideas I've been developing...
如果你需要时间  我可以为你争取
If it's time you need I will buy you time
但你得保证  你下一稿
but you've got to promise me your next-at-bat
得让我下得去手改
is gonna give me something I can work with.
好吧  弗兰克
Okay, Frank.
我会尽力试试
I'll see what I can do.
很好  唐纳德  别为此难过
Good. And Donald, don't let this get you down.
你我合力  能做到
Why? Together we're gonna do more
你这25年都没做到的事
than you've been able to do in 25 years.
现在有两样无关紧要了
Two things are now irrelevant:
唐纳德・布莱斯和他的新草案
Donald Blythe and Donald Blythe's new draft.
最终我还是得亲自出马重新起草
Eventually I'll have to rewrite the bill myself.
勇往直前  这是我的作战口号
Forward! That is the battle cry.
纸上谈兵那一套
Leave ideologies for the Armchair General,
于我无益
does me no good.
沃克刚刚提名了科恩
Walker just nominated Kern.
离确认通过还早呢
It's a long road to confirmation.
科恩身家清白
Kern is a boy scout.
没人是真正清白的  童子军也不例外
Nobody is a boy scout, not even boy scouts.
-你有他什么把柄  -什么都没有
- What do you have? - Absolutely nothing.
那我们还有什么好谈的
Then what are we talking about?
就问一个简单的问题
Just asking the simple question:
你对这份工作有没有兴趣
does the job interest you?
你为什么想要赶走迈克尔
Why would you want Michael gone?
凯茜  你我是"同门"
Cathy, you and I came up together.
外事委员会需要一名能够配合的国务卿
The Foreign Affairs Committee needs a Secretary we can work with,
不怕站出来反驳沃克的错误
someone who isn't afraid to stand up to Walker when he's wrong.
我们需要你
We need you.
假设我有兴趣呢
Let's just assume I am interested.
我不要假设
I do not want to assume.
我要最终答案
I want to know.
2  6
2, 6 ...
好的  2637
Ok ... 2637.
请稍等
Please hold.
佐伊・巴恩斯
Zoe Barnes.
地点你定
Anywhere you want.
马上就来  我回头再找你
On my way. I'm gonna have to call you back.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我拦不到出租车  只能乘地铁
I couldn't get a cab, I had to take a train.
你离开我家之前
Just before you left my house,
回想一下
think back
我们当时在讨论什么
what were we discussing?
-总统的立法议程  -具体一点
- The president's legislative agenda. - Specificly.
教育
Education.
-我说对了吗  -你说呢  巴恩斯小姐
- Was I right? - Do the math, Miss Barnes.
-他需要一份法案  -由谁发起
- He needs a bill. - Sponsored by?
-你  -再想想
- You? - You're smarter than that.
-一个比较权威的人  -很好
- Somebody with legitimacy. - Good.
那么谁在教育问题上最权威
And who screams of legitimacy in education?
-唐纳德・布莱斯  -正确  但问题是
- Donald Blythe? - Correct, the problem is?
他是支持高税收高开支的左派
He's an old school tax and spend liberal.
沃克以温和派竞选
Walker run as a moderate.
你觉得布莱斯会跟我谈吗
You think Blythe would talk to me?
没这必要
He doesn't have to.
等等
Wait.
我们现在处于道德和法律的灰色地带
We are in a very grey area ethically, legally
我个人完全没问题
which I'm okay with...
我很喜欢这幅画  你呢
I just love this painting, don't you?
我们现在是一条船上的人了  佐伊
We are in the same boat now, Zoe.
当心别翻船
Take care not to tip it over,
我只能救一个
I can only save one of us from drowning.
卢卡斯
他周一就要宣布教育改革计划了
He announces the education initiative on Monday.
讲话一半的内容是基于
Half of the address is based on...
-我明白  -我们要去掉这段吗
- I understand. - Do we need to take it out?
没问题的  琳达
We're fine, Linda.
但你才跟我说他需要从头来过
But you just got through saying he has to start over.
不是我选的布莱斯  是你选的
I didn't choose Blythe, you did.
你把他托付给我  要求我创造奇迹
You put him in my lap and ask me to work a miracle,
我会做到  有点信心吧  琳达
and I will. Now have a little faith, Linda.
让我跟唐纳德来搞定它
Let me work with Donald on this.
百日之内能完成  我心里有数
I know what can be accomplished in a hundred days.
好吧  弗兰克
All right, Frank.
-那就全靠你了  -很好
- We're counting on you. - Good.
我想请你帮个小忙
Now I do have a little favor to ask.
杰弗逊舞会上能在我们那桌
Do you think I can get just two more tickets
再安排两个座位吗
for my table at the Jefferson Ball?
来一杯吗
Drink?
好啊  都有什么
Sure, what do you got?
调和威士忌
Whiskey, blent.
恭敬不如从命
If you're offering.
那么
So...
费城那边情况如何
How are things in the city of brotherly love?
还过得去吧
We're getting by.
很好  很好
Good. Good.
抱歉  我弄成纯威士忌了  要我...
Oh, sorry, I've made that neat, did you want...
这样就挺好
It's perfect.
那么
So...
你最近可有点不负责任啊
It seems you've been a bit irresponsible.
什么
What?
别跟我装傻  彼得
Don't play dumb with me Peter.
留着这套应付道德委员会吧
Save it for the Ethics Committee.
喝干吧  你现在需要点勇气
Drink up, you could use a little courage right now.
你不喝吗
You're not having one?
对我来说还早
It's a bit earlier in the day for me.
是那天晚上的事吗
This is about the other night?
你是怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
我是党鞭  职责所在
I'm the whip it's my job to know.
警察放了我
Look, they let me off.
他们不会起诉我  事情都解决了
There's no charges, it's all taken care of.
真是的  彼得
Honestly, Peter,
你真以为这种事自己就能解决吗
do you really think these things just take care of themselves?
是你帮的忙
You?
我就这么一次  我向上帝发誓
I was just this one time, Frank, I swear to God.
那你肯定极不尊重上帝
Then you must hold God in very low esteem.
我们都知道  你在撒谎
Because we both know that's a lie.
招妓  使用禁药  酒后驾车
Solicitation, control of substances, driving under the influence.
嗜好不少啊
Got quite a long list of hobbies.
你想要什么
What is it you want?
你百分百的
Your absolute
无条件的
unquestioning
忠诚
loyalty.
一如既往
Always.
别误解我所说的忠诚
Do not misunderstand what I mean by loyalty.
什么都行  你说吧  弗兰克
Anything. Name it, Frank.
你看起来太随意了
You seem far too relaxed.
我很认真
I'm not.
那就对了
You shouldn't be.
道格会联系你的
Doug'll be in touch.
等会儿
Hang on.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
我一直在给你打电话
I've been calling here,
大家为就职典礼都忙翻了
everybody's been working double time for the inauguration,
你却消失了  你...
you just up and disappear you....
再等会
Hang on.
教育改革草案
我回头打给你
Let me call you back.
-从哪弄来的  -那不重要
- Where did you get this? - Wrong question.
重要的是最快什么时能发到网站上
The right question is how quickly can we get it up on the site.
我得先问过汤姆
I have to run this pass Tom.
我们先咨询一下律师
Let's get legal on this.
确定不触犯法律
Make sure we're not breaking any laws.
-不告诉我消息来源  -我不能
- You won't tell me your source? - I can't do that.
好吧  不过如果有任何法律...
Fine, but if legal finds even one ...
我明白  估计要花多长时间
I understand. How long do you think that will take?
我们最好尽快发到网上
We should get this online right away.
我不能直接扫描三百页的文件
I'm not just going to scan a 300-page document
没仔细读过就摆到网上
and put it up before we have gone through it every...
我都读过了
I did that already.
-全部吗  -从头至尾
- The whole thing? - Cover to cover.
我把摘录和分析
I've got excerpts, analysis,
写成了三千字的稿件  只等校订了
three thousand words ready for editting.
你去仔细校对一下
You start go over that.
让制图部把表格和图表什么的都做好
Get graphics work and table's charts the whole nine yards.
简宁
Janine!
报道角度是什么
What's the angle.
-用两个字概括  -左
- Five words. - Far left of center.
-那是一个字  -极左
- That's four. - Very far left of center.
这能让沃克着急吗
Enough to put Walker on his heels?
岂止  足够让他如坐针毡
Fuck his heels it's gonna put him on his ass.
什么事
What's up?
我们手上有一份教育改革议案的副本
We've got a copy of the administration education bill.
-你帮佐伊做背景调查  -佐伊・巴恩斯
- You gonna work with Zoe, do background cover. - Zoe Barnes?
在这儿
Right here.
听她吩咐
Whatever she needs.
-但应该是我来撰写  -她已经写好了
- Shouldn't I be writting ... - She wrote it already!
我要你反复修改
And I want you to rewrite and rewrite it again.
你来协助她
You'll help her.
汤姆  我才是你的首席政治记者
Tom, I am your chief political correspondent!
快去  我明天就要
Go! I want this by tomorrow.
但我得集中精力报道就职典礼
But I need to focus on the inauguration.
这更重要
This is more important.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
我必忠实执行
That I will faithfully execute the office
合众国总统职务
of the President of the United States.
直播  总统就职典礼
我必忠实执行
That I will faithfully execute the office...
权力正如地产
Power's a lot like real estate.
位置是重中之重
It's all about location, location, location.
你离中心越近
The closer you are to the source,
你的财产就越值钱
the higher your property value.
几百年后  当人们看到这段录像
Centuries from now, when people watch this footage
他们将看到谁在镜头边缘微笑呢
who will they see smiling just at the edge of the frame?
愿上帝助我
So help me God.
祝贺
Congratulations.
直播  总统就职典礼  加勒特・艾伦沃克宣誓就任第45届总统
今天
Today ...
不止关乎未来四年
is not about the next four years
而是关于未来四十年
but about the next four decades.
你们选择信任我
Now, you place your faith in me...
而我
and I, in turn...
则将信念寄托于我们的孩子
choose to place that faith in our children.
我们的孩子是国家未来的关键
Our children are the key to this nation's future.
因此本届政府首先要做的
And that's why the first order of business for this administration
就是推出一项综合教育改革法案
would be a comprehensive education reform bill
调整  资助
to properly fix, finance,
并巩固我国教育
and strengthen our nation's school.
就职演说以教育为基
我向你们保证
And I pledge to you...
我们会在新政府就任一百天内
we will have that bill on the floor of the Congress...
对法案进行投票
within the first one hundred days of this administration.
你能让我们获得邀请真太好了
It was so nice of you to make this possible.
-你给我打电话时  -别这么客气
- When you called me... - Do not say another word.
今年极限飞盘联赛时  我会想艾尔的
I'm gonna miss Al on my ultimate frisbee league this year.
不  我说真的
No, I'm serious.
我们预算委员会的人
A few of us on budget
跟财务委员会的人可挺叫劲的
have quite a rivalry going with the guys on Finance.
比赛十分激烈  我们都动手呢
It's fierce, we get physical.
无论是谁挡在球门线前
Anybody gets between me and that goal line
我都会把那家伙干掉
I will take that sucker down.
唐纳德  我正到处找你呢
Donald! I've been looking for you everywhere!
好伙计  来  我帮你擦擦
Maestro. Here, let me help you with that...
我非常喜欢你的新草案
I really like the work you done on the new draft.
有很大进步  我们将一同创造历史
It'a big step forward, we gonna make history!
谢谢你的鼓励  弗兰西斯
Thanks for the encouragement, Francis.
听着  关于补助  我有几点想法
Listen, I got some ideas about subsidies ...
凯瑟琳  回头再说  唐纳德
Catherine! Hold on to that thought, Donald.
你看起来真太美了
Don't you look stunning.
我们南方女孩脱掉超短牛仔裤
We Southern girls clean up well
穿上些高档衣服
when we get out of our Daisy Dukes,
也能打扮得很好看
and enter some Vera Wang.
我们南方男孩嘴笨
And we southern boys are slow with our words,
但是舞步可灵活得很
but we're fast on our feet.
能有幸邀你共舞吗
May I have the honor?
当然可以
You most certainly may.
弗莱迪烧烤餐馆
-早上好  弗莱迪  -早上好  弗兰克
- Morning, Freddie! - Morning Frank.
-生意好吗  -凑合吧
- How's tricks? - I can't kick.
-要进来吗  -不了  就在外头摆一桌吧
- Want to go on in? - No, why don't you set me up outside.
外头  可是外面很冷
Outside? But it's freezing out here.
这点冷不会冻坏的
Well, a little cold never hurt anybody.
悉听尊便  弗兰克
Anything you say, Frank.
这就上菜
It'll be right up.
我唯一馋的就是上好的肋排
My one guilty pleasure is a good rack of ribs,
即使是在早晨七点半
even at 7:30 in the morning.
这里就我一人
Got the whole place to myself.
弗莱迪有时只为我营业
Freddie sometimes opens up just for me.
在我的家乡  南卡罗莱纳
Where I come from, South Carolina,
人们穷得叮当响
people did have two pennys to rub together.
肋排已经很奢侈了  就像
A rack of ribs was a luxury, like ...
极左教育法案  巨额经费流入左派议题
法案显著加强联邦控制  文  佐伊・巴恩斯
七月里的圣诞节
Christmas in July.
沃克就职  承诺推行教育改革
该死
Fuck...
网站热极了
The website is absolutely crazy.
蓝色佳美特区牌照号WJ0029
Blue Camry DC plate number WJ0029
因肇事撞狗并逃逸被通缉
wanted in connection to canid hit and run
国会警察报案...
code 1057 file by capital...
再来一份吗  弗兰克
Do you want seconds, Frank?
还是算了
I better not.
跟你说  弗雷迪
Tell you what, Freddie?
我要再来一份
Yes I will.
我今天格外饿
I'm feeling a hunger today.
翻译  慢慢
翻译  泽川
翻译  噎死青春
翻译  痒痒
翻译   sakura
翻译  u油
翻译  木月
翻译  ~某人
翻译  小蟹
翻译  小饭
时间轴  名字要很长的萌
时间轴  吉吉
时间轴   Poxle
后期  饿得慌
顾问  老杜
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第一集
人人影视倾情奉献
导演
大卫・芬奇